flipwebsites.com 2010-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Flip Websites

I am committed to protecting your privacy! The only personal information I gather from you is your email address and it is totally voluntary. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your email address is processed and used at FlipWebsites.com (website). I take extraordinary steps to use your email address only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy.

 **Information Collection**  
I am the sole owner of the information collected from this website. I will not sell, share, or rent your information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in my privacy statement below while this website is under my ownership.

 **Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor’s hard drive containing information about the visitor. I do not use cookies but links to my advertisers and other websites may use cookies to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of my advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on my website may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. I do not control the use of cookies or technology used by third parties or the resulting information, and consequently I am not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

 **Log Files**  
I keep simple log files to track what pages visitors have viewed and what links they have clicked on. In no way do these log files capture your personal identification or information.

 **Sharing**  
I do not share any of your personal information (i.e. your email) with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party.

 **Links**  
I am not responsible for privacy policies of other third parties such as advertisers and partner websites linking to or from FlipWebsites.com. Please read the privacy policies of those third parties for information on how they use any personal information you provide them. My privacy policy applies solely to this website. I am not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties.

 **Change of Ownership**  
If this website is ever sold, the new owner will also take ownership of the email addresses collected from this website. The new owner will be responsible to either uphold the current privacy policy in place or change it to his or her own liking.

 **Changes to this Policy**  
I, or any future owner, reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the policy that applied at the time the information was collected.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please [contact me](http://www.flipwebsites.com/contact/).
